todaysinfo.net 2017-07-08

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

 **Version 1.0**

 **  Effective January 15, 2015**

SWEATY ESKIMO, LLC, a California limited liability company (“us”, “our” or “we”), is committed to protecting the privacy and information of users of our websites and services (collectively, the “Services”). We recognize the importance of your privacy and take it very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and handle your information when you use our Services. All of the forms of data, content and information described below are collectively referred to as “information.”

By using our Services, you confirm that have read, understood and agreed to be legally bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

In connection with the Services, we collect the following types of information from you:

 **Personally Identifiable Information (user-provided information)**

Personally identifiable information (“personal information”) is any information that may be used to identify or contact you personally, such as your name, email address, gender, phone number, postal or other physical address. When contacting us for issues related to the Services, users may have the option to submit personal information, which enables us to respond to issues and communicate effectively. The submission of personal information is not required but may be necessary to communicate with you regarding the Services. There may also be other circumstances in which personal information is collected in connection with your use of the Services.

 **Non-Personal Information (automatically collected information which doesn’t identify the user).**

Non-personally identifiable information, such as IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser, search queries, and browsing history, is collected during normal use of the Services. We use browser cookies, storage data, JavaScript, web beacons, pixels, flash cookies, and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information from users of the Services. The tracking technologies collect and pass the collected information with an anonymous unique identifier. Below is a more detained discussion on some of the tehnologies used to collect non-personally identifiable information.

 ** _Cookies_** : When you us the Services, we may send one or more “cookies” (small data files) to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and enable us to help you log in faster and generally enhance your navigation through the Services. Cookies save you time, for example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within the Services, a cookie recalls your specific information on subsequent visits. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the website uses to track the pages you’ve visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A persistent cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to use the Services. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. In addition to enhancing the user experience, we may use cookies to track traffic user traffic patterns. We do this to determine the usefulness and efficiency of our Services and its various pages, and to analyze traffic patterns, in order to constantly improve the Services and better serve our customers.

 ** _Web Beacons_** : When you use the Services, we may employ web beacons (small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your account is collected using these web beacons. In addition, we may also use web beacons in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to analyze the traffic patterns on the website, such as the frequency with which our user visit carious pages of the Services, which ultimately leads to improvements and better content in connection with the Services.

 ** _Log Files_** : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Services, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

 **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use the information that we collect from users of the Services:

  * To provide, maintain, protect and improve the Services;
  * For market research,
  * For security and identification purposes;
  * To provide service and support;
  * To enable certain features of the Services;
  * To contact you as described in this Privacy Policy;
  * To develop new products and services;
  * To notify users of important changes to our Services, including software updates or new features or functionality;
  * To assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you use the Services;
  * To understand how you use and interact with the Services;
  * To provide anonymous individual or aggregate auditing, research, modeling and reporting for our advertisers and other partners (no personally identifiable information about you is shared with our advertisers and other partners as part of these activities); and
  * To provide you with relevant advertising and content;

 **INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or disclose your personal information to third parties except as provided in this Privacy Policy. Your information may be disclosed to third parties only in the following circumstances:

  * We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our Services and/or users of our Services; (c) enforce the terms of use with respect to our Services (including investigation of potential violations thereof); (d) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (e) protect the safety of users of the Services, us or third parties.
  * We may share non-personally identifiable with third parties with whom we work who help us deliver ads, to improve the relevancy of ads when using the Services, and for other purposes related to our business. The third party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interest. The type of information collected by each partner varies. The information practices of these ad companies are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.
  * We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, beta test, analyze, and improve the Services. These third parties may have access to your personal information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

 **OPT-OUT**

If you provide us with personal information, you may notify us at any time to update such information or to let us know if you do not want to receive marketing email or other communications with promotions, special deals, newsletters, etc. You may do this by sending an email to support@todaysdeals.net, or by following the instructions on our website.

 **SECURITY**

Your personal information is protected for your privacy and security. We safeguard the security and confidentiality of the data you send us with physical, technical, and managerial procedures. Please be aware that, despite out best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us.

 **THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our websites may contain links to other websites owned by third parties. Your use of such websites is at your own risk and is subject to the terms of those websites. We have no control over websites that are not ours, and we are not responsible for any changes to or content on them. We assume no responsibility for the content of or services offered by linked third party websites, and make no representations regarding the accuracy of the materials on such websites. Statements made on third party websites linked to or from our websites reflect only the views of their authors and not of us Inclusion on our websites of any third party content or a link to a third party website is not an endorsement of that content or third party website, or any products or sevices offered thereon.

 **LOCATION OF INFORMATION**

 ** ** The Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a user located outside of the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above.

 **CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the modification on the website and/or provide you with notice of the modification. We will also update the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. By continuing to access or use the Services after we have posted such a modification or have provided you with notice of a modification, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If the modified Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease using the Services.

 **PUBLIC FORUMS**

We may offer chat rooms, message boards, blogs, bulletin boards, or similar public forums where you and other users of our Services can communicate. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personal information) in connection with your use of these public forums. We may use personally identifiable and non-personal information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Services.

 **AGE RESTRICTION**

In order to use the Services you must be at least 18 years of age. Persons under the age of 18 are not permitted to use the Services, so this Privacy Policy makes no provision for their use. In the event that a user identifies himself or herself as an individual under the age of 18 within the Site, we will not collect, store or use any personal information of such user. Further, in the event that we receive personal information that we conclude was provided by a person under the age of 18, we will promptly delete such personal information.

 **CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS OR CONCERN  **

For additional inquiries about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please feel free to email us at support@todaysinfo.net
